endeavor.org 2019-05-03

# Privacy Policy - Endeavor

Endeavor Global, Inc. (“Endeavor”) is committed to protecting the privacy of visitors to its web site (the “Site”). The purpose of this Privacy Policy is to inform you of what kinds of information we may gather about you when you visit the Site, how we may use that information, whether we disclose it, and the choices you have regarding our use of and your ability to manage and edit the information. This Privacy Policy applies to the Site. This Privacy Policy does not apply to other web sites to which we link.

#### Our Commitment to Our Donors (“Donor Privacy Policy”)

We will not sell, share or trade our donors’ names or Personal Information with any other entity, nor send mailings to our donors on behalf of other organizations. This Donor Privacy Policy applies to all information received by Endeavor, both online and offline, on any Platform, as well as any electronic, written, or verbal communications.

#### Information Collection

We collect personal information when you wish to use certain features of the Site, such as registering as a user, requesting newsletters, making a donation or sending feedback, comments or other information to us. When you choose to use these features, we ask for information such as your name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number, and other personal information (“Personal Information”). We use Personal Information for the following general purposes: to fulfill your requests for certain services offered through the Site, to create personal accounts, to send users publicity materials or other general information about Endeavor, to meet any applicable legal and regulatory requirements, and to respond to any feedback you submit.

Through the Site, we may automatically gather certain information about the use of the Site, such as how frequently certain areas of the Site are visited including through the use of cookies, web beacons and other technologies.

You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser (such as Internet Explorer or Mozilla Firefox) settings. Each browser is a little different, so look at your browser Help menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookie settings. If you turn cookies off, you may not have access to many features that make your site experience more efficient and some of our services may not function properly.

For more information about cookies, please see www.allaboutcookies.org.

#### Protecting Personal Information

When you give Endeavor Personal Information, we take steps to ensure that your information is treated securely. Endeavor uses industry-standard encryption technologies when transferring and receiving sensitive visitor data via the Site. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your Personal Information, Endeavor cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us, and you do so at your own risk. Once we receive your transmission, we use commercially reasonable efforts to ensure its security on our systems, and to protect against the loss, misuse, or alteration of information that we have collected.

#### Disclosure

Unless otherwise stated in this Privacy Policy, we do not sell, trade or rent your Personal Information to others. We may permit certain trusted partners to access your information in connection with their performance of services to maintain and operate the Site and certain features on the Site. We do not otherwise disclose any Personal Information or any information about your individual visits to our site except when we believe in good faith (i) that the law requires such disclosure or (ii) that such disclosure is necessary to protect the rights and property of Endeavor or others.

We allow you to opt out of receiving e-mail from us. If you no longer wish to receive emails from us, you may opt-out of receiving them by emailing us at [info@endeavor.org](mailto:info@endeavor.org).

We use non-personally identifiable information in the aggregate so that we can improve the Site and for business and administrative purposes. We may use or share with third parties for any purpose aggregated data that contains no personally identifiable information. Our website may share information with companies that provide support services to us (such as web hosts) or that help us publicize our services (such as email vendors). These companies may need information about you in order to perform their functions. These companies are not authorized to use the information we share with them for any other purpose. Except as otherwise stated above, we will not publish or provide your e-mail address or other personal information to third parties without your consent.

#### Updating Personal Information and Preferences

If you have provided us with personal information and would like to change, correct, or request access to your personal information or update or cancel your registration, you may do so by emailing us at [outreach@endeavor.org](mailto:outreach@endeavor.org).

#### Children

We do not solicit any personal information from children under the age of 13. We encourage families to obtain additional information about safe use of the Internet at ftc.gov/kidzprivacy. We reserve the right to change our Privacy Policy for the Site at any time. If we decide to change our Privacy Policy, we will post the revised Privacy Policy so that you will know what information we gather, how we might use that information and whether we will disclose it to anyone. Please check periodically to keep informed of any changes. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of any changes to this Privacy Policy constitutes acceptance of those changes.

If you have questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy, please contact us at:

Endeavor Global, Inc.  
900 Broadway, Suite 301  
New York, NY 10003
